{
    "id": "346dfe11cd1b4f74a1e7837d25d1ce5c",
    "title": "Prepositions Quiz 2",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d6610c35beab439c8540d1d6612dbc94",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The boy walked ——————– the road.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "along",
                        "on",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The river flows ——————- the bridge.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "below",
                        "under",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The work was done —————– haste.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "in",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He died —————– his country.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "on",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The steam engine was invented —————— James Watt.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "by",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The robbers jumped —————– the compound wall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "across",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The village was destroyed —————— fire.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "by",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He spoke —————- me —————— French.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with, in",
                        "to, in",
                        "at, in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They live —————— the same roof.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "under",
                        "within"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have not seen him ——————– last Wednesday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}